

DENIZ YOZGATLI

Address: Askabat St. No 61D-3/18 Cankaya/Ankara

Phone: +90 538 402 1203

Email: denizyozgatli@outlook.com

SUMMARY

I graduated from Ege University, Department of Statistics in 2024. Since I am interested in software and finance, I chose courses related to these fields during my undergraduate studies. In addition to the education I received at my university, I also pursued training aimed at meeting the needs of the industry in order to develop myself in the field of data science. My career goal is to gain experience, improve myself, and increase my proficiency in the fields of statistics and data science, while producing value-added work in these areas.

EDUCATION

Ege University 2018 - 2024

Department of Statistics

GPA: 3.29

WORK EXPERIENCE

Acadebi Platform 2020 - 2021

· Product marketing

Statistics Research Group 2020 - 2023

Social media management

PROJECTS

Examining the Nutritional Habits of University Students During the

Coronavirus Pandemic

• The aim of this research is to examine the nutritional habits of Ege University students during the coronavirus period.

Price Prediction of the Top 10 Companies Providing the Most

Employment in the BIST100 Index Using Machine Learning in Python

• The aim of the study is to predict the prices of 10 companies listed on Borsa Istanbul using LSTM by leveraging their past price movements.

SKILLS

Data Preprocessing

Python

SPSS

· Data Visualization

SQL

Matlab

Machine Learning

R

MS Office Apps

CERTIFICATIONS

Python A-Z: Data Science and Machine Learning

2023

· Introduction to Data Science with R

2024

Python and Tensorflow for Data Science

2024